Hi everyone! Yes, I have a new hair color. Ouch, ouch, ouch. And Nono is here again.
Ow! Hey, what are you doing? Okay, but I pre-recorded some videos with the red hair, so don't worry.
You'll see more of it in other videos. But yeah, this is my new hair color. I like it pretty much.
There's something I want to talk to you about today concerning YouTube and my channel and my future plans here.
So yeah, because I'm kind of done with YouTube.
Okay, where to start? I have to say I'm really disappointed. I'm kind of angry and I'm really done with all these superficial and prude guidelines here on YouTube
because my enthusiasm and my motivation kind of jumped out of the window this week
because something happened here on YouTube and I was like, what the f***?
And I'm going to tell you what it was and what my future plans are
because I may not continue with YouTube the way I used to
and I want to be honest with you and tell you why.
I'm fed up with YouTube but not with you because you're a lovely community
and thanks for your support and that you're watching my videos so this has nothing to do
with you as my viewer so just wanted to make that clear okay so yeah I earned money with
youtube you may have noticed that because you saw advertisements in front or during my videos
and it was by far not enough to make a living out of it god knows uh no but the money I earned
with YouTube I kind of reinvested in YouTube so I bought a new camera last
year bought new lenses from my old camera I bought a lot of jumpsuits for
example and shoes which I showed in my videos and if you upload a video then
YouTube kind of classifies your videos into a green and orange category like
advertiser friendly green so yes suited for all advertisers and not suited for
advertisers which is kind of orange and like I don't know on Monday I could
watch my videos turn from green to orange like kind of one by one I could
refresh the page and it was another video orange which means not suitable
for all advertisers which means also that there are no ads at the videos
anymore which means I don't earn any money with these videos it had like
really to my whole channel there's not a single video left which is advertiser
friendly green whatever and I was like what just happened here because I didn't
get a notification I got nothing from YouTube and so I wrote a message to
YouTube support and asking like yeah what what's happening here because yeah
all my videos are demonetized and I don't know why and they said like yeah
I know we'll have to check we'll get back to you soon and then I got an
answer and I said like my channel has a significant number of videos that are
violating the advertiser friendly guidelines I was like what why because
from all the over 60 videos I uploaded I think four of them were like an orange not suited for
all advertisers and I was totally okay with that because some were a bit too fetishy and and others
I kind of showed too much booty which is yeah kind of weird anyway but whatever they were like yeah
and because a lot of videos violated these guidelines then we'll just turn your whole
channel down and I was like what why what can I do to change that again what can I do to I don't know
be more precise in the future to make sure it's advertiser friendly and they just said like the
same thing again which did not really help me and I still don't know what exactly happened and
why it happened and whatever which is really messed up I really feel kind of helpless but
YouTube was like yeah that's it you have to live with that good luck bye I also don't know if my
uploads are going to be advertiser friendly ever again no one told me I don't know if my whole
channel gets taken down at some point because they say I am violating all the guidelines or
whatever no guarantee okay one thing they sent with this last answer was like
here here are some links now you can have a look at them and one of the links
is content and guidelines about nudity and sexual content policies and I was like
what. So maybe I think I'm kind of, I don't know, too fetishy for YouTube or they don't like what
I'm doing somehow. So theory number one I have is that with the really successful LeoHacks video
some algorithm came up with the idea to check my channel again and rated some videos orange and
And then YouTube was like, okay, we have to check the whole channel.
And the other theory is that more viewers kind of reported my videos because they didn't
like them or whatever.
And then someone from YouTube had a look at my channel and I don't know, personal preferences,
whatever, didn't like it and turned my whole channel to an orange monetization.
But as I already said, I don't know for sure and I'll probably never know.
Okay so to sum this up, I think this whole fruitish, vague, official, advertiser friendly
YouTube guidelines are kind of interpretation thing.
I experienced something similar on Instagram.
Instagram didn't like my latex pictures as well because apparently it was too shiny and
they didn't show my pictures to my audience anymore.
So I'm guessing my content is too sexually explicit, whatever, for this prudish American
social media platforms.
I don't really know.
After this happened I was like two days really down and I thought like what am I going to
do?
Of course now the money from the videos is missing so I'm probably not able to buy as
much stuff for my YouTube videos to show you but on the other hand it's not all about the
money but about the whole thing that went down that they really didn't tell me what
to do and what I did wrong and what happened here and it is just so demotivating and I
don't know what I'll do in the future exactly as I said I already have a few videos recorded
I won't stop this channel but I think I'll publish a few less videos or fewer videos.
I think fewer videos is the grammatically correct term because somehow it was also a
wake up call.
I was really obsessed with YouTube.
I was checking the stats daily and how many people review my videos and what can I do
next and I was really like in this whole machinery where I had to record new videos on a regular
basis so I could post videos on a regular basis and it was really stressful to be honest and I was
really like I don't know if I had that much fun anymore because I do have a full-time job I'm
doing this in my free time and it was really a bit too much by the end and I have to take a step
back because apparently what I'm doing is not something I can really like financially successfully
do on YouTube because they apparently don't like it so I should do it really just for fun.
I am just continuing as I think and I'm not quitting YouTube but I'll see what I'll do.
So of course you'll see the catsuit videos I am doing with the help of my Ko-fi supporters.
There is going to be a black latex catsuit and some other latex catsuit and a red PVC catsuit in the future.
I'm very happy that I can show you these.
YouTube probably won't like them but I don't care because I'll keep doing what I do.
And even if it's offensive or indecent for some people or some might think it's improper, I don't care.
I will show you that and I also have some collaborations going on which I'll continue.
On a side note, if you see the advertisement label on my videos, it does not mean that I get paid
for doing these videos. It only means that I can like keep the products I'm showing you. But since
there is a weird law in Germany, I have to label these videos as advertisement. So this is all that
the advertisement label means. Just wanted to mention that. Okay, I guess that's it. That's
what I want to tell you. Thank you for watching this video. To YouTube I have to say I'm really
disappointed and I'm really done with you but I hope you, my viewers, are going to have a lot of
fun with the videos I'm going to upload in the future and I hope we're going to have fun together.
Have a nice day. See ya. Bye.